<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ferrari</title>
        <description></description>
        <link>https://ferrari.bokemia.com/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://ferrari.bokemia.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:48:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:48:24 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.2.2</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>31 things</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;01&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;01.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that you don’t mind the fact that I’ve told my family about you. To me, that means your boyfriend would never feel trapped and urged into hiding things from either side, except for what’s reasonably private or sensitive, obviously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;02&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;02.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that you are a mother first and foremost, all the while never forgetting about yourself. It’s a hard thing to pull off and it commands admiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;03&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;03.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how your smile is a signature personality trait. You express your concerns, fears and sorrows, but you keep your spirit up no matter how they make you feel, no matter what.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;04&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;04.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how you style your hair. It makes you shine, every single day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;05&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;05.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that you’re not picky about food. Your enjoyment of eating is far more related to the company around you than the meal itself. A person spending that time with you feels like they’re special as a result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;06&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;06.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that you want what your boys want, and don’t trace a path in advance for them. You listen, respond and act on that feeling. The house project is a good example of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;07&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;07.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that you loved Loki and constantly reminded people of how she was best approached. You always treated her the same way I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;08&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;08.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that you are sophisticated, not complicated. And because of that, you inspire me to do what I want at any given moment. To name but one thing, the looming clock in my tattoo concept, which implies both the acceptance of who I am and the urgency to act on it, came from my discussions with you. It just struck me one day; you are my clock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;09&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;09.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how you speak the truth directly, and yet in a way that’s constantly adorned by kindness. It inspires those around you to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;10&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;10.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how you look in both high heels and running shoes. You are just as pretty either way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;11&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;11.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how you listen to people and wait until they’re done speaking before you react. It makes them feel comfortable and ignites their willingness to share more about themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;12&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;12.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the texture of your skin. I confess I’ve stolen all peeks of it that I could find, and they set my blood to blaze and turn my way of thinking upside down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;13&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;13.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the energy you deployed when we walked together. There’s a physical strength to your stance that I greatly enjoyed seeing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;14&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;14.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how you hug me and let me hold you tight for a while longer. The feeling I get from being close to you is something many search for, but rarely find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;15&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how knowing you is loving you. Falling in love with you was the easiest thing I ever did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;16&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;16.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like that I can tell you anything without ever dreading to be misunderstood or judged. Talking to you is easy, enjoyable, addictive and void of any surprising reaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;17&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;17.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like how close I am to having a fucking heart attack every single time I see you. It feels amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;18&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;18.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the way you look at me. You make me feel like I’m worth a hundred billion bucks and that anything is possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;19&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#05a377&quot;&gt;19.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the way you react to compliments, with such a unique blend of diffidence and charm. It creates a compulsion to give you more and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Green_02.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>https://ferrari.bokemia.com/jennifer</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://ferrari.bokemia.com/jennifer</guid>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>